David Scott Bowen / 606.349.4085 / scott 1993@hotmail.com

Portfolio: https://davidscottbowen.github.io/

Summary: An IT Manager with 15 years experience in a busy office environment. I have spent the last 3 years building software development skills necessary to gain a rewarding career in software development.

Skills

- HTML/CSS/Javascript
- Swift/iOS
- Agile/SCRUM
- Git version control
- iOS Team Lead
- Teaching Assistant/Management

Experience

JANUARY 2017 - PRESENT

Interapt, Paintsville, KY - iOS Developer

- Assigned to this position after TEKY educational instruction was complete
- Deployed documentation for iOS app development
- Contributed to 4 iOS apps

SEPTEMBER 2016 - JANUARY 2017

TEKY Initiative - Teaching Assistant

- Wrote 4 HTML/JAVASCRIPT Apps
- Wrote 2 iOS Apps
- 16 weeks of software development instruction: Swift, iOS, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

MARCH 2003 - AUGUST 2016

Mineral Labs Inc - Information Technology Manager

- Network maintenance
- WebSite development

Education

Eleven Fifty Academy, Paintsville, KY - SEPTEMBER 2016 - JANUARY 2017

Received Gold and Red Badge certificate for completion of coding standards.

Morehead State University, Morehead, KY - AUGUST 2012 - MAY 2016

Bachelor degree in Computer Information Systems.